// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question:"The scores of a student in five subjects are 80, 85, 90, 95, and 100. What is the mean score?",
  answer: "92",
  options: [
    "91",
    "92",
    "95",
    "99"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "In a group of 10 people, the ages are 20, 22, 23, 25, 25, 26, 27, 28, 30, and 32. What is the median2 ",
  answer: "25",
  options: [
    "21",
    "24",
    "25",
    "29"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "The scores of a basketball team in a tournament are 78, 82, 86, 90, and 94. What is the mode of the scores?",
  answer: "4 hrs",
  options: [
    "1 hrs",
    "9 hrs",
    "5 hrs",
    "4 hrs"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: "A bus covers a distance of 360 miles at an average speed of 40 miles per hour. How long does it take to complete the journey?",
  answer: "9 hrs",
  options: [
    "11 hrs",
    "9 hrs",
    "10 hrs",
    "4 hrs"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: "In a set of data, the median is 15. If a value of 20 is added to the data, what will happen to the median?",
  answer: " It will increase",
  options: [
    " It will increase",
    " It will decrease",
    "It will remain the same",
    "Cannot be determined"
  ]
},


   {
 numb: 6,
 question: "The heights of a group of students are 150 cm, 160 cm, 170 cm, 180 cm, and 190 cm. What is the mode of the heights?",
  answer: "No mode",
  options: [
    "173 cm",
    "179 cm",
    "170 cm",
    "No mode"
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 7,
  question: "The marks obtained by a class of 30 students in a test are 80, 85, 85, 90, and 95. What is the mean mark?",
   answer: "86",
   options: [
    "80",
    "82",
    "86",
    "88"
  ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "In a set of data, the mean is 25 and the median is 30. What is the mode?",
     answer:"10 hrs",
     answer: "No mode",
  options: [
    "173",
    "179",
    "170",
    "No mode"
  ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "The ages of a family are 30, 32, 35, 40, and 45. What is the median age?",
       answer: "4 hrs",
       answer: "35",
        options: [
          "31",
          "34",
          "35",
          "39"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 10,
        question: "The weights of a group of students are 50 kg, 55 kg, 60 kg, 65 kg, and 70 kg. What is the mean weight?",
        answer: "64",
        options: [
          "61",
          "64",
          "65",
          "69"
        ]
        }
];